

Contact

Phone

+923122053864

Email

daniyalaslam544@gmail.com

Address

House # L/23 Gulshan-e-Iqbal 13D Karachi Sindh

Education

2018- 2020 Intermediate TABS College Hyderabad

2021 - present
Software Engineering
University of Sindh

Daniyal Aslam

Front-End Developer

Profile

Hey there!

Its Daniyal Aslam i am a web developer, I have been doing web development since last 2 years. I have worked with various programming languages and framworks including HTML5, CSS3 ,Bootstrap 4, SASS, Javascript ES6,JQuery WORDPESS. and React.js

I have good command over the skills I mentioned above.
I can develop web applications, develop all kind of
websites. E-commerce and Business websites etc.
Intense Knowledge of JavaScript.
Excellent knowledge of OOP.

- PSD to HTML
- XD to HTML
- Figma to HTML

Experience

2021 - Present Front-End Developer

Digital Elliptical

2020 - 2021

Tegnite solution

Front-End Developer

2019 - 2020

Freelance Front-End Developer

Portfolio

http://18.221.104.204/daniyal https://theteamfreelance.com/

https://thecodeicon.com/ https://www.prevep.com/

https://teqnite.com/aucto/ https://erpminsights.com/

Skills

HTML5 CSS3 JQuery JQuery Mordpress Node.js